<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Admost API Documentations on Documentation for Admost API Services</title>
    <link>/amrapi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Admost API Documentations on Documentation for Admost API Services</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/amrapi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>User Ad Revenue</title>
      <link>/amrapi/user-revenue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/amrapi/user-revenue/</guid>
      <description>User Ad Revenue Ad Revenue You can get user ad revenue information without ad network
Network Base Ad Revenue You can get user ad revenue information with ad network
 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publisher Applications</title>
      <link>/amrapi/publisher-app-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/amrapi/publisher-app-api/</guid>
      <description>Publisher&amp;rsquo;s application informations  URL : https://partners.admost.com/v3/apps?key=[key]
METHOD : GET
Request Parameters    Name Type Description     key string Publisher Token    Response    Name Description     app_id Admost Application ID   name Application Name   package_name Application bundle id/package name   platform (ios, android etc.)    Response Status Codes    Code Description     200 OK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjust Raw Data Export Settings</title>
      <link>/amrapi/adjust-raw-data-export/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/amrapi/adjust-raw-data-export/</guid>
      <description>InfoYou can find Adjust SDK integration document on their help page.
 With this raw data export settings, we&amp;rsquo;ll able to get paid campaign installs from Adjust. We need the APP token of the application and API token
WarningFacebook Campaigns
On October 29th 2021, Facebook deprecated their Advanced Mobile Measurement (AMM) program. This means that Facebook Marketing Partners and advertisers may not receive device-level campaign data for any iOS users attributed to Facebook, and only partial data for Android users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service Subscription Credentials &amp; Settings</title>
      <link>/amrapi/subscription/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/amrapi/subscription/</guid>
      <description> Apple Tells how to get credential and activate realtime subscription notification in apple store
Google Tells how to get credential and activate realtime subscription notification in google play
 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Server to Server Rewarded Structure</title>
      <link>/amrapi/server-to-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/amrapi/server-to-server/</guid>
      <description>With this integration, you can be sure whether the user is watching a rewarded video or not. In case of watching the rewarded video successfully, a callback is made to the publisher url.
You should active some s2s settings on admost dashboard.
 Add your endpoint and generate customer s2s verification token.   My Apps -&amp;gt; Edit App
  Activate s2s from Rewarded zone
    Publisher URL: Callback URL identified by the publisher on admost dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impression and Revenue API</title>
      <link>/amrapi/impression-revenue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/amrapi/impression-revenue/</guid>
      <description> Application&amp;rsquo;s placement and country base impression and revenue data  Endpoint: http://amr-api.admost.com/api/publisher/v1/reporting?apiKey=[apiKey]&amp;amp;startdate=[YYYY-MM-DD]&amp;amp;enddate=[YYYY-MM-DD]&amp;amp;app=[appid]
METHOD : GET
Request Parameters    Name Type Description     apiKey string Publisher&amp;rsquo;s token   startdate string Report start date   enddate string Report end date   appid string Admost application ID    Response    Name Description     AdNetwork Ad Network Name   AppName Application Name   AppType Application type android/ios   Placement Placement Name   CountryCode Country short code   Country Country Name   Impression Impression count   Revenue Revenue amount ($)   Date Which day the data belongs to    </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohort Analysis API</title>
      <link>/amrapi/cohort-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/amrapi/cohort-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Endpoint: http://amr-api.admost.com/api/publisher/v1/cohort
METHOD : POST
Request Parameters    Name Type Description     apiKey string Publisher&amp;rsquo;s token   startdate string Start date (yyyy-MM-dd)   enddate string End date (yyyy-MM-dd)   groupBy string Comma seperated values (day, week, month, app, country, source, campaign, adgroup, creative, source_type, test)   apps string Filters app ids (comma seperated, can be found on Admost Dashboard -&amp;gt; My Apps)   appType string Filters app type (Allowed values (&amp;ldquo;android&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;ios&amp;rdquo;))   userType string Filters user type (Allowed values (&amp;ldquo;organic&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;paid&amp;rdquo;))   revenueType string Filters revenue type (Allowed values (&amp;ldquo;adRevenue&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;inAppPurchase&amp;rdquo;))   countries string Filters countries (comma seperated, ISO 3166-1 alpha-2 )   countryIn string Determines how the values of previous parameter is used, Allowed values (&amp;ldquo;in&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;notin&amp;rdquo;), &amp;ldquo;in&amp;rdquo; is default   sources string Filters sources (comma seperated)   sourceIn string Determines how the values of previous parameter is used, Allowed values (&amp;ldquo;in&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;notin&amp;rdquo;), &amp;ldquo;in&amp;rdquo; is default   campaigns string Filters campaigns (comma seperated)   adgroups string Filters adgroups (comma seperated)   creatives string Filters creatives (comma seperated)   tests string Filters A/B tests (comma seperated)   minCohortSize integer Filters cohort size which are greater than the value specified   revenueCostRatioDay integer Filters rows which has day N revenue/cost ratio greater or less than following parameter   revenueCostRatioPercent integer Filters rows which has day N revenue/cost ratio greater or less than specified %   revenueCostRatioType integer Allowed values(&amp;ldquo;min&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;max&amp;rdquo;)   retentionFilterDay string Filters rows which has day N retention greater or less than following parameter   retentionFilterPercent integer Filters rows which has day N retention greater or less than specified %   retentionFilterType string Allowed values(&amp;ldquo;min&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;max&amp;rdquo;)   currency string Currency, ISO 4217 alpha-3, Default value USD   showExpected boolean Allowed values (true,false)   showAllDays boolean Allowed values (true,false)    Request Example curl --location --request POST &amp;#39;http://amr-api.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>